Are you ready? Are you ready for the
dance? Step number one:
Turn off your phone.
We're going through the new one,
and when we're beyond the fourth stage of the
formless realm, then
we go to the lama. The apprenticeship of the camp—the
majority of the lama is very interesting
because the lama is supposed to teach you something
you don't yet know. But you
create this lama;
that's really interesting. So you create
someone who teaches you something you don't yet know,
and that's the teaching of the
lama. You also create it. How can it be that
you create a lover
who teaches you something you don't
yet know?
The second chamber law—who said that?
The second chamber law—in the same way that you
can make a lot of money by helping someone else
make a little money,
you can create a lover who can teach
you something you don't yet
know. And that's the apprenticeship of the
camp. So, the majority of the lama does
n't mean his head is empty;
maybe it is.
Can we record the meditation today
and make it available on the site?
I would like two  We
want to make independent recordings because the demons
will destroy one of them,
so we're going to, so we're going to,
level 10, the meditation on the
apprenticeship.
We could also meditate on the apprenticeship of the
partner who
screamed at each other last night, but the apprenticeship of
his teacher is a great
emptiness of karma, and we will
use the teacher's apprenticeship to
repeat what he learned about karma. So why did we
choose against
teachers? Because I want you to go back
to your past lives and
continue to develop this film.
After a month, like, chat, what's up?
After a month, what's up?
This film about your
past lives should be like a
Japanese epic, a 1.4-hour film.
I want you to continue what we're doing now,
and part
of it, perceiving the apprenticeship, is also
why you were born here. What
is the reason you were born here?
What is the reason you
met your teacher? This is a
meditation on the Wheel of Life. So
traditionally, the
Wheel of Life is the theme after  You danced the
Lion's Dance, so
today we will also do the Lion's Dance.
Then we will do the Teacher's Teaching Time,
and part of the Teacher's Heid
is: Where do they come from? What was there?
Then we go back to the
Lama's face because it brings very good luck. The
Lama's face.
We have
repeated all of this over and over again. When you meditate on the
Teacher's face, you concentrate on his
eyes, and that the eyes
live you. Three very important things are coming in.
Please open the door. One
student, two cappuccinos.
It's instant karma for me. Immediately.
We will finish it.
So we end with the loving eyes
of the Teacher, and please don't start
moving and getting stuck when I
say, "Make the last three long
exhalations.
Make three long exhalations, one quick one that looks
like golden light."
So if you are a great yogi,
you can also imagine that it comes from the
third eye because the nostrils
are impure. The air comes from the
nostrils.  But imagine it
comes from the third eye, so please do
n't move until we've finished the
three exhalations in the dedication. For
those who want to go further,
I'll explain after the meditation;
there are additional steps you
can incorporate.